Guide to the Cornell University College of Architecture, Art, and Planning Records, 1905-2004
College of Architecture, Art, and Planning, Cornell University, Records, 1905-2004
- Series I. Administrative/departmental files
  - Architecture, Faculty Dinners, 1928-1929 (Box 7)
  - Architecture - new building, 1928-1929 (Box 7)
  - Arts and Sciences, Faculty of, 1928-1929 (Box 7)
  - A.C.S.A., 1928-1929 (Box 7)
  - Ba, 1928-1929 (Box 7)
  - Be-Bi, 1928-1929 (Box 7)
  - Bl-Bo, 1928-1929 (Box 7)
  - Br-By, 1928-1929 (Box 7)
  - B.A.I.D., 1928-1929 (Box 7)
  - Bosworth, F.H. (personal), 1928-1929 (Box 7)
  - Bradford, E.F. - Admissions Office, 1928-1929 (Box 7)
  - B[rochure] R[equests], 1928-1929 (Box 7)
  - Buildings and Grounds, 1928-1929 (Box 7)
  - Ca-Cl, 1928-1929 (Box 7)
  - Co-Cy, 1928-1929 (Box 7)
  - Camden, Harry P., 1928-1929 (Box 7)
  - City Planning, 1928-1929 (Box 7)
  - College Entrance Examination Board, 1928-1929 (Box 7)
  - Committee on Purchase, 1928-1929 (Box 7)
  - Committee on Student Records, 1928-1929 (Box 7)
  - Competition, 1928-1929 (Box 7)
  - Comptroller - C.D. Bostwick, 1928-1929 (Box 7)
  - D, 1928-1929 (Box 7)
  - Davis, E. Gorton, 1928-1929 (Box 7)
  - Davis, E. Gorton (personal), 1928-1929 (Box 7)
  - Design Grades, 1928-1929 (Box 7)
  - Draftsmen Wanted, 1928-1929 (Box 7)
  - E, 1928-1929 (Box 7)
  - Entrance Credits, 1928-1929 (Box 7)
  - Exhibitions, 1928-1929 (Box 7)
  - F, 1928-1929 (Box 7)
  - Faculty Meetings Minutes and Memoranda, 1928-10-1933-06 (Box 82)
  - Fellowships or scholarships, 1928-1929 (Box 7)
  - Fine Arts Building proposal memorandum 2, 1928-12-15 (Box 82)
  - Fuertes Memorial Contest, 1928-1929 (Box 7)
  - Ga-Gn, 1928-1929 (Box 7)
  - Go-Gy, 1928-1929 (Box 7)
  - Gifts and Prizes - Baird, Dickinson, 1928-1929 (Box 7)
  - Graduating Class - data on, 1928-1929 (Box 7)
  - Graduate Fellowships and Scholarship Applications, 1928-1929 (Box 7)
  - Graduate School, 1928-1929 (Box 7)
  - Ha, 1928-1929 (Box 7)
  - He-Hi, 1928-1929 (Box 7)
  - Ho, 1928-1929 (Box 7)
  - Hu-Hy, 1928-1929 (Box 7)
  - Honor System, 1928-1929 (Box 7)
  - I, 1928-1929 (Box 7)
  - Infirmary Reports, 1928-1929 (Box 7)
  - J, 1928-1929 (Box 7)
  - Ka-Ki, 1928-1929 (Box 7)
  - Kl-Ky, 1928-1929 (Box 7)
  - La-Ll, 1928-1929 (Box 7)
  - Lo-Ly, 1928-1929 (Box 7)
  - Landscape Admissions - E. Gorton Davis, 1928-1929 (Box 7)
  - Lawson, Edward (personal), 1928-1929 (Box 7)
  - Lectures, 1928-1929 (Box 7)
  - Library, 1928-1929 (Box 7)
  - Library of Periodicals, 1928-1929 (Box 7)
  - Lowenstein, Milton, 1928-1929 (Box 7)
  - Ma-Me, 1928-1929 (Box 7)
  - Me-Mi, 1928-1929 (Box 7)
  - Mo-My, 1928-1929 (Box 7)
  - Martin, C.A. (personal), 1928-1929 (Box 7)
  - Medical Advisor, 1928-1929 (Box 7)
  - Military Training, 1928-1929 (Box 7)
  - N, 1928-1929 (Box 7)
  - Notices, 1928-1929 (Box 7)
  - O, 1928-1929 (Box 7)
  - P, 1928-1929 (Box 7)
  - Phelps, Professor A.C. (personal), 1928-1929 (Box 7)
  - Power, Ethel B. (House Beautiful) - inc. items on Margaret Bourke-White, 1928-1929 (Box 7)
  - Q, 1928-1929 (Box 7)
  - Ra-Ri, 1928-1929 (Box 7)
  - Ro-Ry, 1928-1929 (Box 7)
  - Registrar, 1928-1929 (Box 7)
  - Sc-Sm, 1928-1929 (Box 7)
  - Sn-Sy, 1928-1929 (Box 7)
  - Sanderson, 1928-1929 (Box 7)
  - Schedule, 1928-1929 (Box 7)
  - Schroth, William H., 1928-1929 (Box 7)
  - Schucharot, W.H., 1928-1929 (Box 7)
  - Secretary, 1928-1929 (Box 7)
  - Shreve, R.H., 1928-1929 (Box 7)
  - Statistics, 1928-1929 (Box 7)
  - Summer Session, 1928-1929 (Box 7)
  - Ta-Ti, 1928-1929 (Box 7)
  - To-Ty, 1928-1929 (Box 7)
  - Teaching Positions Open, 1928-1929 (Box 7)
  - Telegrams, night letters, long distance calls, etc., 1928-1929 (Box 7)
  - Todd, C.L. (personal), 1928-1929 (Box 7)
  - Todd, Walter L., 1928-1929 (Box 7)
  - Traveling Exhibition, 1928-1929 (Box 7)
  - Traveling Fellowship, 1928-1929 (Box 7)
  - Treasurer, 1928-1929 (Box 7)
  - Trowbridge, A.B., 1928-1929 (Box 7)
  - U-V, 1928-1929 (Box 7)
  - U.S. Mint, 1928-1929 (Box 7)
  - University Faculty, 1928-1929 (Box 7)
  - University Policy, Committee on, 1928-1929 (Box 7)
  - Van Vleck, Ernest A., 1928-1929 (Box 7)
  - Wa-Wi, 1928-1929 (Box 7)
  - Wo-Wy, 1928-1929 (Box 7)
  - X-Y-Z, 1928-1929 (Box 7)
  - A, 1929-1930 (Box 8)
  - American Academy in Rome, 1929-1930 (Box 8)
  - A.S.L.A., 1929-1930 (Box 8)
  - Architect's House, 1929-1930 (Box 8)
  - Architecture, Faculty of, 1929-1930 (Box 8)
  - Architecture, Faculty dinner, 1929-1930 (Box 8)
  - A.C.S.A., 1929-1930 (Box 8)
  - B, 1929-1930 (Box 8)
  - B.A.I.D., 1929-1930 (Box 8)
  - Bosworth, F.H. (personal), 1929-1930 (Box 8)
  - Bradford, E.F. (Admissions Office), 1929-1930 (Box 8)
  - B[rochure] R[equests], 1929-1930 (Box 8)
  - Burnett, T.R., 1929-1930 (Box 8)
  - C, 1929-1930 (Box 8)
  - Clarke, Gilmore D., 1929-1930 (Box 8)
  - Cohen, John J., 1929-1930 (Box 8)
  - The Fine Arts project, 1929-03-04 (Box 82)
    The relation of site to program and proposed structure
  - Hurd, Thaddeus B., 1929-1930 (Box 8)
  - Kohn, Robert D., 1929-1930 (Box 8)
  - Schedules, 1929-1930 (Box 8)
  - State Board for Registration of Architects - F.H. Bosworth, 1929-1930 (Box 8)
  - Young, George Jr. (personal) - inc. items pertaining to Margaret Bourke-White, 1929-1930 (Box 8)
  - Z, 1929-1930 (Box 8)
  - A, 1930-1931 (Box 8)
  - Ackerman, F.L., 1930-1931 (Box 8)
  - American Academy in Rome, 1930-1931 (Box 8)
  - A.I.A., 1930-1931 (Box 8)
  - Annual Report, 1930-1931 (Box 8)
  - Architecture, Faculty of, 1930-1931 (Box 8)
  - B, 1930-1931 (Box 8)
  - B.A.I.D., 1930-1931 (Box 8)
  - Black, Russell V., 1930-1931 (Box 8)
  - Bosworth, F.H. (personal), 1930-1931 (Box 8)
  - B[rochure] R[equests], 1930-1931 (Box 8)
  - Brockway, Albert L., 1930-1931 (Box 8)
  - Buildings and Grounds, 1930-1931 (Box 8)
  - C, 1930-1931 (Box 8)
  - Camden, Harry P., 1930-1931 (Box 8)
  - City Planning, 1930-1931 (Box 8)
  - Clarke, Gilmore D., 1930-1931 (Box 8)
  - Committee on Purchases, 1930-1931 (Box 8)
  - Co-op, 1930-1931 (Box 8)
  - D, 1930-1931 (Box 8)
  - Design Degrees, 1930-1931 (Box 8)
  - E, 1930-1931 (Box 8)
  - Elective Courses, 1930-1931 (Box 8)
  - Equipment, 1930-1931 (Box 8)
  - Exhibition, 1930-1931 (Box 8)
  - F, 1930-1931 (Box 8)
  - Fellowships or shcalorships, 1930-1931 (Box 8)
  - Flack, Harols - Cornellian Council, 1930-1931 (Box 8)
  - Fleming, Bryant, 1930-1931 (Box 8)
  - G, 1930-1931 (Box 8)
  - Gifts and Prizes - Baird, Dickinson, Sampseri, 1930-1931 (Box 8)
  - Graduate School, 1930-1931 (Box 8)
  - Graduating Class, data on, 1930-1931 (Box 8)
  - H, 1930-1931 (Box 8)
  - J, 1930-1931 (Box 8)
  - K, 1930-1931 (Box 8)
  - L, 1930-1931 (Box 8)
  - Landscape Advisory Council, 1930-1931 (Box 8)
  - Landscape Architecture, 1930-1931 (Box 8)
  - Lawson, Edward, 1930-1931 (Box 8)
  - Lectures, 1930-1931 (Box 8)
  - Library, 1930-1931 (Box 8)
  - M, 1930-1931 (Box 8)
  - Martin, C.A., 1930-1931 (Box 8)
  - N, 1930-1931 (Box 8)
  - Notices, 1930-1931 (Box 8)
  - O, 1930-1931 (Box 9)
  - P, 1930-1931 (Box 9)
  - Peaslee, Horace W., 1930-1931 (Box 9)
  - R, 1930-1931 (Box 9)
  - Registrar, 1930-1931 (Box 9)
  - S, 1930-1931 (Box 9)
  - Secretary's Office, 1930-1931 (Box 9)
  - Shreve, Harold R., 1930-1931 (Box 9)
  - Summer Session, 1930-1931 (Box 9)
  - T, 1930-1931 (Box 9)
  - Telegrams, night letters, long distance, etc., 1930-1931 (Box 9)
  - Traveling Exhibition, 1930-1931 (Box 9)
  - Treasurer's Office, 1930-1931 (Box 9)
  - U, 1930-1931 (Box 9)
  - University Faculty, 1930-1931 (Box 9)
  - University Fellowships, 1930-1931 (Box 9)
  - University Policy, Committee on, 1930-1931 (Box 9)
  - V, 1930-1931 (Box 9)
  - W, 1930-1931 (Box 9)
  - Y, 1930-1931 (Box 9)
  - Young, George Jr. (personal), 1930-1931 (Box 9)
  - A, 1931-1932 (Box 9)
  - Ackerman, Fred C., 1931-1932 (Box 9)
  - Alumni Bulletin, 1931-1932 (Box 9)
  - American Academy in Rome, 1931-1932 (Box 9)
  - A.I.A., 1931-1932 (Box 9)
  - A.S.L.A., 1931-1932 (Box 9)
  - Announcements, 1931-1932 (Box 9)
  - Architecture, Faculty of, 1931-1932 (Box 9)
  - A.C.S.A., 1931-1932 (Box 9)
  - B, 1931-1932 (Box 9)
  - B.A.I.D., 1931-1932 (Box 9)
  - Bosworth, F.H. (personal), 1931-1932 (Box 9)
  - B[rochure] R[equests], 1931-1932 (Box 9)
  - Buildings and Grounds, 1931-1932 (Box 9)
  - C, 1931-1932 (Box 9)
  - Clarke, Gilmore D., 1931-1932 (Box 9)
  - Comptroller, 1931-1932 (Box 9)
  - D, 1931-1932 (Box 9)
  - Design Grades, 1931-1932 (Box 9)
  - Draftsmen Wanted, 1931-1932 (Box 9)
  - E, 1931-1932 (Box 9)
  - F, 1931-1932 (Box 9)
  - Fellowships and scholarships other than Cornell University, 1931-1932 (Box 9)
  - Fontainbleau School - Application Blanks, etc., 1931-1932 (Box 9)
  - G, 1931-1932 (Box 9)
  - Gifts and Prizes, 1931-1932 (Box 9)
  - Goeller, Charles, 1931-1932 (Box 9)
  - Graduate fellowships and scholarships, 1931-1932 (Box 9)
  - Graduating Class, data on, 1931-1932 (Box 9)
  - H, 1931-1932 (Box 9)
  - Hartell, John H., 1931-1932 (Box 9)
  - Honor Book, 1931-1932 (Box 9)
  - I, 1931-1932 (Box 9)
  - Infirmary Report, 1931-1932 (Box 9)
  - J, 1931-1932 (Box 9)
  - K, 1931-1932 (Box 9)
  - L, 1931-1932 (Box 9)
  - Landscape Architecture, 1931-1932 (Box 9)
  - Lawson, Edward, 1931-1932 (Box 9)
  - Lazenby, Petrorne D., 1931-1932 (Box 9)
  - Lectures, 1931-1932 (Box 9)
  - Library, 1931-1932 (Box 9)
  - M, 1931-1932 (Box 9)
  - Martin, C.A., 1931-1932 (Box 9)
  - Martin's successor, 1931-1932 (Box 9)
  - Mid-term tests, 1931-1932 (Box 9)
  - Military Training, 1931-1932 (Box 9)
  - N, 1931-1932 (Box 9)
  - Notices, 1931-1932 (Box 9)
  - P, 1931-1932 (Box 9)
  - R, 1931-1932 (Box 9)
  - S, 1931-1932 (Box 9)
  - Secretary's Office, 1931-1932 (Box 9)
  - Shreve, R. Harold, 1931-1932 (Box 9)
  - Summer Session, 1931-1932 (Box 9)
  - T, 1931-1932 (Box 9)
  - Teaching positions open in other universities and colleges, 1931-1932 (Box 9)
  - Telegrams, night letters, long distance, etc., 1931-1932 (Box 9)
  - Traveling Exhibitions, 1931-1932 (Box 9)
  - Treasurer's Office, 1931-1932 (Box 9)
  - U, 1931-1932 (Box 9)
  - University Faculty, 1931-1932 (Box 9)
  - University Policy, Committee on, 1931-1932 (Box 9)
  - V, 1931-1932 (Box 9)
  - Veterans of Foreign Wars - George Young (personal), 1931-1932 (Box 9)
  - W, 1931-1932 (Box 9)
  - Webster, Evan L., 1931-1932 (Box 9)
  - Young, George Jr. (personal), 1931-1932 (Box 9)
  - A, 1932-1933 (Box 10)
  - Aboretum, 1932-1933 (Box 10)
  - American Academy in Rome, 1932-1933 (Box 10)
  - A.I.A., 1932-1933 (Box 10)
  - American Society of Landscape Architects, 1932-1933 (Box 10)
  - Architecture, Faculty of, 1932-1933 (Box 10)
  - A.C.S.A., 1932-1933 (Box 10)
  - B, 1932-1933 (Box 10)
  - B.A.I.D. - Architecture, 1932-1933 (Box 10)
  - B.A.I.D. - Fine Arts, 1932-1933 (Box 10)
  - Board of Trustees (George Young, Jr.), 1932-1933 (Box 10)
  - Bradford, E.F., 1932-1933 (Box 10)
  - Buildings and Grounds, 1932-1933 (Box 10)
  - C, 1932-1933 (Box 10)
  - Clarke, Gilmore D., 1932-1933 (Box 10)
  - Comptroller, 1932-1933 (Box 10)
  - D, 1932-1933 (Box 10)
  - Design Grades, 1932-1933 (Box 10)
  - E, 1932-1933 (Box 10)
  - Exhibitions, 1932-1933 (Box 10)
  - F, 1932-1933 (Box 10)
  - Fellowships and Scholarships (non-Cornell), 1932-1933 (Box 10)
  - Fleming, Bryant, 1932-1933 (Box 10)
  - Flack, Harold - Cornellian Council, 1932-1933 (Box 10)
  - G, 1932-1933 (Box 10)
  - Graduate fellowships and scholarships, 1932-1933 (Box 10)
  - Graduate School, 1932-1933 (Box 10)
  - Graduating Class - data on, 1932-1933 (Box 10)
  - H, 1932-1933 (Box 10)
  - Hurd, T.B. (personal), 1932-1933 (Box 10)
  - Infirmary, 1932-1933 (Box 10)
  - J, 1932-1933 (Box 10)
  - K, 1932-1933 (Box 10)
  - L, 1932-1933 (Box 10)
  - Lectures, 1932-1933 (Box 10)
  - Library, 1932-1933 (Box 10)
  - Library - Carnegie Corporation Fund, 1932-1933 (Box 10)
  - M, 1932-1933 (Box 10)
  - Martin, 1932-1933 (Box 10)
  - Martin, C.A. (personal), 1932-1933 (Box 10)
  - Mathematics Department, 1932-1933 (Box 10)
  - Military Training, 1932-1933 (Box 10)
  - N, 1932-1933 (Box 10)
  - Notices, 1932-1933 (Box 10)
  - O, 1932-1933 (Box 10)
  - P, 1932-1933 (Box 10)
  - Pearse, G.E., 1932-1933 (Box 10)
  - Popham, Walter D., 1932-1933 (Box 10)
  - R, 1932-1933 (Box 10)
  - Registrar, 1932-1933 (Box 10)
  - S, 1932-1933 (Box 10)
  - Secretary's Office, 1932-1933 (Box 10)
  - Shreve, R.H., 1932-1933 (Box 10)
  - T, 1932-1933 (Box 10)
  - Telegrams, 1932-1933 (Box 10)
  - Todd, Conway, L., 1932-1933 (Box 10)
  - Traveling Exhibitions, 1932-1933 (Box 10)
  - Treasurer's Office, 1932-1933 (Box 10)
  - University Policy, 1932-1933 (Box 10)
  - V-W, 1932-1933 (Box 10)
  - Y-Z, 1932-1933 (Box 10)
  - Young, George Jr. (personal), 1932-1933 (Box 10)
  - Board of Trustees, 1933-1934 (Box 10)
  - Faculty Meetings Minutes and Memoranda, 1933-10-1937-06 (Box 82)
  - "That Necessary Evil, The Architectural Engineer" - article by Thomas H. McKaig, 1933-1934 (Box 10)
  - Young, George Jr. (personal), 1933-1934 (Box 10)
  - A, 1934-1935 (Box 10)
  - Acceptances, Students, 1934-1935 (Box 10)
  - Admissions, 1934-1935 (Box 10)
  - Alumni Breakfast, June 1935 (Box 10)
  - A.C.S.A., 1934-1935 (Box 10)
  - American Academy in Rome, 1934-1935 (Box 10)
  - A.I.A., 1934-1935 (Box 10)
  - A.I.A. Politics, 1934-1935 (Box 10)
  - Architecture, Faculty of, 1934-1935 (Box 10)
  - Architecture, Registration, 1934-1935 (Box 10)
  - B, 1934-1935 (Box 11)
  - Bailey, Claude, 1934-1935 (Box 11)
  - B.A.I.D., 1934-1935 (Box 11)
  - Black, Russel, V., 1934-1935 (Box 11)
  - Board of Trustees, 1934-1935 (Box 11)
  - Borgeson, M.B., 1934-1935 (Box 11)
  - Buildings and Grounds, 1934-1935 (Box 11)
  - C, 1934-1935 (Box 11)
  - Clarke, Gilmore D., 1934-1935 (Box 11)
  - Cornellian Council, 1934-1935 (Box 11)
  - D-E-F, 1934-1935 (Box 11)
  - Design Grades, 1934-1935 (Box 11)
  - Dunbar, William, 1934-1935 (Box 11)
  - Entrance Data - Freshmen, 1934-1935 (Box 11)
  - Equipment, 1934-1935 (Box 11)
  - Exhibitions, 1934-1935 (Box 11)
  - Federal Emergency Relief Administration, 1934-1935 (Box 11)
  - Fellowship Applications, 1934-1935 (Box 11)
  - Fellowships and scholarships other than Cornell, 1934-1935 (Box 11)
  - G, 1934-1935 (Box 11)
  - Goeller, C.L. (personal), 1934-1935 (Box 11)
  - Graduate School, 1934-1935 (Box 11)
  - H-I-J, 1934-1935 (Box 11)
  - Hartell, J.A. (personal), 1934-1935 (Box 11)
  - Honor drawings returned Spring, 1934 (Box 11)
  - K-L, 1934-1935 (Box 11)
  - Lawson, E. (personal), 1934-1935 (Box 11)
  - Lectures, 1934-1935 (Box 11)
  - Library, 1934-1935 (Box 11)
  - M-N, 1934-1935 (Box 11)
  - Models - working second term, 1934-1935 (Box 11)
  - Montillon, E.D., 1934-1935 (Box 11)
  - Notices, 1934-1935 (Box 11)
  - O, 1934-1935 (Box 11)
  - Orchids, 1934-1935 (Box 11)
  - P, 1934-1935 (Box 11)
  - Pealsee, Horace, 1934-1935 (Box 11)
  - R, 1934-1935 (Box 11)
  - Regional Planning inquiries received, 1934-1935 (Box 11)
  - Registrar's Office, 1934-1935 (Box 11)
  - S, 1934-1935 (Box 11)
  - Secretary's Office, 1934-1935 (Box 11)
  - Shreve, R. Harold, 1934-1935 (Box 11)
  - T, 1934-1935 (Box 11)
  - Teaching Positions - open in other colleges and universities, 1934-1935 (Box 11)
  - Telegrams, 1934-1935 (Box 11)
  - Tilton, J.N. (personal), 1934-1935 (Box 11)
  - Todd, Conway L., 1934-1935 (Box 11)
  - Traveling Exhibition, 1935 (Box 11)
  - Treasurer's Office, 1934-1935 (Box 11)
  - U-V-W, 1934-1935 (Box 11)
  - University Faculty, 1934-1935 (Box 11)
  - University Placement Committee, 1934-1935 (Box 11)
  - University Policy, 1934-1935 (Box 11)
  - Budgets, 1936-1950 (Box 81, Folder 1-14)
  - College of Architectural Council, 1936-1937 (Box 11)
  - Enrollment Statistics - University State of New York, 1936-1937 (Box 11)
  - Group Insurance, 1936-1937 (Box 11)
  - Jackson, F. Ellis, 1936-1937 (Box 11)
  - Todd, Conway L., 1936-1937 (Box 11)
  - Women Graduates, 1936-1937 (Box 11)
  - Board of Trustees, 1937-1938 (Box 11)
  - Cranbrook Academy of Art - Cranbrook Scholarship, 1937-1938 (Box 11)
  - Faculty Meetings Minutes and Memoranda, 1937-09-1944-06 (Box 82)
  - Mathematics Department, 1937-1938 (Box 11)
  - Accredited Secondary Schools, 1938-1939 (Box 11)
  - Admission Data, 1938-1939 (Box 11)
  - Admissions - qualified students, 1938-1939 (Box 11)
  - Alumni Letters Data, 1938-1939 (Box 11)
  - American Academy in Rome, 1938-1939 (Box 11)
  - A.I.A., 1938-1939 (Box 11)
  - Announcement of Architecture, 1938-1939 (Box 11)
  - Architecture, Faculty of, 1938-1939 (Box 11)
  - A.C.S.A., 1938-1939 (Box 11)
  - Board of Trustees, 1938-1939 (Box 11)
  - Card-Caitlin Scholarship in Architecture, 1938-1939 (Box 11)
  - Clements, Miss Gabrielle - collection of etchings, 1938-1939 (Box 11)
  - Committee on Student Records, 1938-1939 (Box 11)
  - Comptroller, 1938-1939 (Box 11)
  - Deficiencies Entrance, 1938-1939 (Box 11)
  - Equipment, 1938-1939 (Box 11)
  - Exhibitions, 1938-1939 (Box 11)
  - General Correspondence A-Z (5 folders), 1938-1939 (Box 11)
  - Graduate School - Dean Richtmyer, 1938-1939 (Box 11)
  - Martin, C.A. (personal), 1938-1939 (Box 11)
  - National Council of Architecture Registration Board, 1938-1939 (Box 11)
  - New York Society of Architects, 1938-1939 (Box 11)
  - Notices, 1938-1939 (Box 11)
  - Paris Prize Traveling Exhibition, 1938-1939 (Box 11)
  - Payroll Blanks, 1938-1939 (Box 11)
  - Positions Opened, 1938-1939 (Box 11)
  - Prospective Students - blue cards returned, 1938-1939 (Box 11)
  - Requests for Announcements of Architecture, 1938-1939 (Box 11)
  - Rome Collaboration Competitions - American Academy in Rome, 1938-1939 (Box 11)
  - Secretary's Office, 1938-1939 (Box 11)
  - Summer School Programs, 1938-1939 (Box 11)
  - Traveling Exhibitions, 1938-1939 (Box 11)
  - Treasurer's Office, 1938-1939 (Box 11)
  - Trustee action on fellowships and scholarships, 1938-1939 (Box 11)
  - Universtiy Fellowships, 1938-1939 (Box 11)
  - Admissions - qualified students, 1939-1940 (Box 12)
  - Alumni Letter, 1939-1940 (Box 12)
  - Announcement, 1939-1940 (Box 12)
  - A.C.S.A., 1939-1940 (Box 12)
  - B.A.I.D., 1939-1940 (Box 12)
  - Buildings and Grounds, 1939-1940 (Box 12)
  - College of Arts and Sciences - Fine Arts Major, 1939-1941 (Box 12)
  - Detweiler, H.A., 1939-1941 (Box 12)
  - Eidlitz, Fred, 1939-1941 (Box 12)
  - Graduate School, 1939-1941 (Box 12)
  - History Professor - Arts and Architecture, 1939-1941 (Box 12)
  - President of the University, 1939-1941 (Box 12)
  - Speeches, Articles, etc., 1937-1940 (Box 12)
  - Statistics, 1939-1940 (Box 12)
  - Traveling Exhibitions, 1939-1940 (Box 12)
  - Admissions Correspondence, 1940-1941 (Box 12)
  - American Academy in Rome, 1940-1941 (Box 12)
  - A.I.A. Central New York Chapter, 1940-1941 (Box 12)
  - A.I.A. Student Medal, 1940-1941 (Box 12)
  - Applicants' correspondence for positions in college, 1940-1941 (Box 12)
  - Architecture Advisory Board, 1940-1941 (Box 12)
  - Architecture, Faculty of, 1940-1941 (Box 12)
  - Board of Trustees, 1940-1941 (Box 12)
  - Boochever, L.C., 1940-1941 (Box 12)
  - Books of Information, 1940-1941 (Box 12)
  - Budget, 1940-1941 (Box 12)
  - Buildings and Grounds, 1940-1941 (Box 12)
  - Competitions, 1940-1941 (Box 12)
  - Exhibitions, 1940-1941 (Box 12)
  - Faculty Advisors, 1940-1941 (Box 12)
  - Fine Arts Department, 1940-1941 (Box 12)
  - Graduate School, 1940-1941 (Box 12)
  - Graduating class, data on, 1940-1941 (Box 12)
  - Harris, Mrs. R.S., 1940-1941 (Box 12)
  - Interschool Programs, 1940-1941 (Box 12)
  - Librarian, 1940-1941 (Box 12)
  - Library, 1940-1941 (Box 12)
  - Mackesey, Thomas, 1940-1941 (Box 12)
  - New York Society of Architects, 1940-1941 (Box 12)
  - Positions Opened, 1940-1941 (Box 12)
  - President of the University, 1940-1941 (Box 12)
  - Prospective Faculty, 1940-1941 (Box 12)
  - Requests for Announcements, 1940-1941 (Box 12)
  - Rome Collaborative Competitions, 1940-1941 (Box 12)
  - Scarab Fraternity - the Scarab Gold Medal, 1940-1941 (Box 12)
  - Secretary's Office, 1940-1941 (Box 12)
  - Shreve, Lamb, Harmon - Professional Fellowship, 1940-1941 (Box 12)
  - Student Conduct Committee, 1940-1941 (Box 12)
  - Students needing financial aid, 1940-1941 (Box 12)
  - Teaching positions open in other universities and colleges, 1940-1941 (Box 12)
  - Thesis Committee, 1940-1941 (Box 12)
  - Tilton, John N., Jr. - corres. re: college work, 1940-1941 (Box 12)
  - Tilton, John N., Jr. - Armstrong, Furst, and Tilton, 1940-1941 (Box 12)
  - Tilton, John N., Jr. - Personal File, 1940-1941 (Box 12)
  - Traveling Exhibits, 1940-1941 (Box 12)
  - Treasurers Office, 1940-1941 (Box 12)
  - University Faculty, 1940-1941 (Box 12)
  - University Placement Bureau, 1940-1941 (Box 12)
  - Visiting Critic, 1940-1941 (Box 12)
  - Admissions - qualified students, 1941-1942 (Box 13)
  - American Acadmey in Rome, 1941-1942 (Box 13)
  - A.I.A., 1941-1942 (Box 13)
  - A.I.A. Central New York Chapter, 1941-1942 (Box 13)
  - A.I.A. Student Medal, 1941-1942 (Box 13)
  - A.S.L.A., 1941-1942 (Box 13)
  - Announcement, 1941-1942 (Box 13)
  - A.C.S.A., 1941-1942 (Box 13)
  - Board of Trustees, 1941-1942 (Box 13)
  - Budget, 1941-1942 (Box 13)
  - Buildings and Grounds, 1941-1942 (Box 13)
  - Clarke, G.D., 1941-1942 (Box 13)
  - College of Architecture Council, 1941-1942 (Box 13)
  - Competitons, 1941-1942 (Box 13)
  - Degree of Master and Regional Planning, 1941-1942 (Box 13)
  - Exhibitions, 1941-1942 (Box 13)
  - Mental Ability Test, 1941-1942 (Box 13)
  - Positions Opened, 1941-1942 (Box 13)
  - President of the University, 1941-1942 (Box 13)
  - Prospective Faculty, 1941-1942 (Box 13)
  - Summer Sketching Requirement, 1941-1942 (Box 13)
  - Tilton, John N., Jr., 1941-1942 (Box 13)
  - Tilton, John N., Jr. - corres. re: college work, 1941-1942 (Box 13)
  - Traffic Council Commission, 1941-1942 (Box 13)
  - Treasurers Office, 1941-1942 (Box 13)
  - Admissions, 1942-1943 (Box 13)
  - Admissions Correspondence, 1942-1943 (Box 13)
  - Announcements of Architecture, 1942-1943 (Box 13)
  - Board of Trustees, 1942-1943 (Box 13)
  - Buildings and Grounds, 1942-1943 (Box 13)
  - Design Programs - bound volumes, 1942-1943 (Box 13)
  - General Correspondence A-F, 1942-1943 (Box 13)
  - General Correspondence G-L, 1942-1943 (Box 13)
  - General Correspondence M-R, 1942-1943 (Box 13)
  - General Correspondence S-Z, 1942-1943 (Box 13)
  - Graduate School, 1942-1943 (Box 13)
  - Interschool Programs, 1942-1943 (Box 13)
  - Lectures, 1942-1943 (Box 13)
  - Library, 1942-1943 (Box 13)
  - McMullen Scholarships - Mr. Summers, 1942-1943 (Box 13)
  - Military Training, 1942-1943 (Box 13)
  - New York State Association of Architects, 1942-1943 (Box 13)
  - Notices, 1942-1943 (Box 13)
  - Phi Kappa Phi, 1942-1943 (Box 13)
  - Positions Opened, 1942-1943 (Box 13)
  - President of the University, 1942-1943 (Box 13)
  - Proposed Curriculum, 1942-1943 (Box 13)
  - Registration for Selective Service, 1942-1943 (Box 13)
  - Rome Collaborative Competitions, 1942-1943 (Box 13)
  - Secretary's Office, 1942-1943 (Box 13)
  - Stone, Walter King, 1942-1943 (Box 13)
  - Student Council Committee, 1942-1943 (Box 13)
  - Student Records, Council of Keeping, 1942-1943 (Box 13)
  - Student War Service Committee, 1942-1943 (Box 13)
  - Summer Term, 1942 (Box 13)
  - Thesis Committee, 1942-1943 (Box 13)
  - Traveling Exhibits, 1942-1943 (Box 13)
  - Treasurers Office, 1942-1943 (Box 13)
  - University Faculty, 1942-1943 (Box 13)
  - Visiting Critics, 1942-1943 (Box 13)
  - Budget, 1943-1944 (Box 13)
  - Curtiss-Wright Program, 1943-1944 (Box 13)
  - V-1 Programs, 1943-1944 (Box 13)
  - Faculty Meetings Minutes and Memoranda, 1944-08-1950-06 (Box 82)
  - Gibbs, Harrison, 1944-1945 (Box 13)
  - Lawson, Edward, 1944-1945 (Box 13)
  - Folder with loose sheets, n.d. (Box 13)
  - Faculty Meetings Minutes and Memoranda, 1950-10-1955-06 (Box 83)
  - Faculty Meetings Minutes and Memoranda, 1955-10-1960-06 (Box 83)